The catalyst is finally ready to go.
It's a project I've been wanting to do
for a really long time and I honestly
just finally made it a priority and got
it done. It is and always will be
completely free. It's a big mission of
mine and has been for almost 15 years to
make as many things as affordable and
accessible when possible as I can. So,
this is a way for you to know what I
think is cool in the area of health and
human performance. It'll be really
practical stuff. It'll be really
complicated stuff. It's just a
combination of anything I found to be
valuable, interesting, or entertaining.
It's nutrition stuff or exercise tips,
new research articles that were just
published that I thought were really
good or helpful. And so, it's a really
[music] short, quick bite into those
with direct access and links for anyone
who wants to go into more detail for any
of the topics you found interesting.
We're also going to be giving away lots
of features, tons [music] of giveaways,
and all kinds of other stuff. So, I hope
you enjoy it. It's the Catalyst, and it
is available now. What's up team? The
Catalyst newsletter with Dr. Annie
Galpin and I is now live. [music]
This is a free newsletter, but it's
going to operate every little bit like a
paid newsletter because you're going to
get exclusive access to content that you
won't find anywhere else. You're going
to get access to what studies we're
reading, training, nutrition, and
supplement tips that aren't anywhere
else. And if you like my research
reviews here on Instagram, I'm doing
video reviews for subscribers only
inside of the newsletter. and so [music]
much more. There's a lot of stuff coming
down the pipe for you guys. And this is
a big part of what we want to do. We
want to give back to science like we
always have. And we want to take people
on a journey as if they were getting
mentored by us, as if they were keeping
up to date with exactly [music] what
we're doing and learning so that you can
stay on top of the science. And just as
importantly, stay on top of the
application on that science. The
catalyst is here and it's not going
anywhere.